geeksmack.net 2010-08-15

# Privacy Policy | GeekSmack

We can be reached via e-mail at [ ](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language=%27JavaScript%27%20type=%27text/javascript%27%3E%20%3C%21--%20var%20prefix%20=%20%27mailto:%27;%20var%20suffix%20=%20%27%27;%20var%20attribs%20=%20%27%27;%20var%20path%20=%20%27hr%27%20+%20%27ef%27%20+%20%27=%27;%20var%20addy50707%20=%20%27staff%27%20+%20%27@%27;%20addy50707%20=%20addy50707%20+%20%27geeksmack%27%20+%20%27.%27%20+%20%27net%27;%20document.write%28%20%27%3Ca%20%27%20+%20path%20+%20%27%5C%27%27%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy50707%20+%20suffix%20+%20%27%5C%27%27%20+%20attribs%20+%20%27%3E%27%20%29;%20document.write%28%20addy50707%20%29;%20document.write%28%20%27%3C%5C/a%3E%27%20%29;%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%20%3Cscript%20language=%27JavaScript%27%20type=%27text/javascript%27%3E%20%3C%21--%20document.write%28%20%27%3Cspan%20style=%5C%27display:%20none;%5C%27%3E%27%20%29;%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language=%27JavaScript%27%20type=%27text/javascript%27%3E%20%3C%21--%20document.write%28%20%27%3C/%27%20%29;%20document.write%28%20%27span%3E%27%20%29;%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[staff@geeksmack.net](mailto:staff@geeksmack.net) This e-mail address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it .

### Advertisements

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at staff [at] geeksmack.net. At GeekSmack, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy d ocument outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by GeekSmack and how it is used.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.geeksmack.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
GeekSmack does use cookies to store information about visitor’s preferences, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on GeekSmack .:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to GeekSmack and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include

  * Google Adsense
  * Adphilia

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on GeekSmack send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

GeekSmack has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. GeekSmack’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Regards to Personal Information

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name and e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, disclosed when legally required to do so at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at the above address.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them.

Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. However, hacking is a risk that every website faces, and, should your information be lost or stolen should the site be hacked, GeekSmack cannot be held responsible.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above email address.

Some icons used on this website are part of the [Fugue](http://www.pinvoke.com/) icon set, used under a [Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported license](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/3.0/).
